Hello, My name is Derek Mont-Ros. I am a graduate of Florida International University where I obtained my Bachelors in Arts. I strive to become a digital designer for companies big or small. I am a creative Graphic Artist and Designer with a talent for developing unique custom artwork. I have been known for having innovative approaches to ideas and concept development. I have nearly 3 years of expertise overseeing individual projects and brand development collections. I always strive to consistently create skilled, clear and brand-specific designs.

Work History

2019-11 -Current

Operations Specialist

Florida International University, Modesto A. Maidique Campus, MAIMI, FLORIDA

- Motivated and trained employees to maximize team productivity.
- Evaluated performance and policies against metrics.
- Collected, arranged and input information into database system.
- Enforced regulatory and company policy compliance to improve workplace and employee safety and readiness.
- Encouraged and promoted ideas aligned to business needs and benefits.
- Managed transportation on and off work premises for civilians and customers alike.
- Developed 30 effective improvement plans in 2019-2021

2019-11 -Current

Sign Maker

Florida International University, Modesto A. Maidique Campus, MIAMI, FL

- Completed finish trimming, grommeting and hemming on signage.
- Maintained clean and tidy shop space for maximum customer appeal, safety and organization.
- Designed new sign graphics and layouts to match customer specifications.
- Installed vinyl on vehicle doors, windows, and body

DEREK MONT-ROS

GRAFIC ARTIST

Contact

Address

Homestead, United States, 33033

Phone

(786) 877-9279

E-mail

dereksandvich@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/derek-mont-r

WWW

https://www.instagram.com/skull101ify/?hl=en

Skills

Visual design

Excellent

PC and Mac platforms

Excellent

Digital design

Excellent

Logo design

Very Good

Photography composition

Good

Digital imagery

- panels for partial coverage or complete wraps.
- Assembled interior signs and added tactile or braille additions to substrate.
- Created custom signs for customers with quality builds and careful installation.
- Imported customer designs into software and verified dimensions, checked for errors and made corrections.
- Maintained counts and lifts, shifts and stocks materials and parts.
- Planned and paced work efficiently in order to meet daily, weekly, project or production goals.
- Executed entire assembly process by accurately interpreting set-up sheets, work orders, drawings or blueprints.
- Recognized and reported defective material and equipment to shift supervisor.
- Built containers and packed parts in accordance with detailed packing specifications.

2019-11 -Current

Transportation Driver

Florida International University, Modesto A. Maidique Campus, MIAMI, FL

- Worked under pressure and met deadlines while maintaining composure in difficult situations.
- Drove excellent guest service for events and conducted evaluations after completion.
- Completed routine pre- and post-trip inspections to evaluate vehicles and assess maintenance needs.
- Achieved consistent safety targets by adjusting driving to different road and traffic conditions, balancing loads and avoiding dangerous driving actions.
- Upheld high standards of professionalism and discretion when working with high-value clients.
- Cleaned and maintained vehicle and assessed vehicle for damage after each shift.
- Planned and adjusted optimal routes based on traffic and weather conditions.
- Assisted passengers with entering and exiting vehicles safely and securely stowed baggage to minimize damage risk.



2017-12 -2019-04

EVENTS TEAM MEMBER

Miami Dade College Kendall Campus, MIAMI, FL

- Performed post-event tasks such as breaking down areas, removing trash and cleaning facilities.
- Provided exceptional customer service to all guests and escalated concerns where needed.
- Set up event facilities and equipment, cleaned areas and organized supplies.
- Talked to coworkers using electronic devices such as computers and radios.
- Utilized great communication and interpersonal skills when interacting with parties to promote smooth and efficient operations.
- Worked in operations, accomplishing all assigned tasks with efficiency and accuracy.

Education

2019-09 - **Bachelor of Arts: Graphic Design**2021-12 Florida International University - Miami, FL

2017-09 -2019-08 Associate of Arts: Computer Graphics

MIAMI DADE COLLEGE - Miami, FL

Accomplishments

Obtained Eagle Rank in Boy Scouts of America in 2017.
Continuously made Dean's List every semester.
Member of Phi Beta Kappa Honor Society.
3.5 GPA.

Affiliations

I have been affiliated briefly with the Phi Theta Kappa Honors Society of Florida International University, a long time Volunteer of Ponce De Leon Middle scool from March 2010-August 2019, and as previously mentioned served a vast amount of time as a member of the Boy Scouts of America.

Additional Information

I am proficient in lesser known mobile digital manipulation applications such as Faceapp and Picsart. I also have a large social media platform with more than ten thousand followers with the Instagram handle @Skull101ify. I am extremely passionate about designing as a whole which includes (but is not limited to) banners, posters, signs, and logos.

Certifications

Adobe Dreamweaver License-2017

Interests

I am extremely interested in all fields of cinematography, photo manipulation, digital editing, and digital design. My passions include graphic novels, video games, movies, and shows which all pertain to my skill set within the digital world.